(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-06T13:36:31.400183",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
It was music that brought me to this country.
In the undulating whirlwind of life, it's only normal to seek some place you belong...
...and that place you belong is often underscored by...
a thing that you like. A thing that draws you in and gives you an identity.
But I had obligations. Ya know, stuff to do.
Stuff I HAD to do.
It's funny how liking one thing can lead to loving another thing.
That was the case with me, actually.
Walking around, confused, bored... Lost, I guess.
And then, just like that- there's a moment where... it clicks.
It clicks, and suddenly, you're different. Different in some way you can't explain.
A rabbit hole appears before you.
And you see how far it takes you.
照らしてってmoonlight 目を奪ってブルーライト
Let the moonlight shine on us, let the blue light daze our eyes
ネオンサインが呼ぶ表裏
Two sides neon signs have revealed
連れ去ってmidnight 血走ったredeyes
Sweep us away into midnight, bloodshot red eyes
大人達の子守唄
This lullaby goes out to the adults
なんせ俺達の夜は忙しい keep on dancin'
You know, it's gon' be a busy night, keep on dancin'
さぁ鬼の居ぬ間に
C'mon while all the demons are away
俺達の夜は忙しい oh yeah
It's gon' be a busy night oh yeah
なんせ俺達の夜は忙しい keep on dancin'
You know, it's gon' be a busy night, keep on dancin'
さぁ鬼の居ぬ間に
C'mon while all the demons are away
俺達の夜は忙しい oh yeah
It's gon' be a busy night oh yeah
ガキの頃から夜が好きだった
I've liked the night since I was a brat
9時に寝るのはなんか嫌だった
Hated to go to bed before nine
なんことなくただ勿体なかった
Simply ain't only so much for me
お前の事がもっと知りたかった
Wished I'd known more about you
いわゆる三文の徳投げ売ってでも見たいのさもっと奥の奥の奥
Let me witness what's deeper inside
十二オクロックから丑の刻まで初めてお前を跨いだのは
Late in the night, 12 to 2
いや初めて跨いだのは確か14俺は何も知らねえワナビィ
Nah that was about 14 I first mounted you
手取り足取り全てが新しい姿形にその香り静けさが似合うその黒い方に吸い込まれてた
Every step, every move look like a brand-new thing
手招きされるままに
Your appearance and your smell
それからお前は音楽をくれた女の裸も見せてくれた
Even silence would suit your dark skin
飲んだ事ねえ酒に口づけしてオトンのタバコくすね火を付けた
I was hooked on it as you lured me in
ヤバい気配漂うアングラでシークレットエリアにまみれて
And you gave me music
よふかしのうた 照らしてってmoonlight 目を奪ってブルーライト
Let the moonlight shine on us, let the blue light daze our eyes
ネオンサインが呼ぶ表裏
Two sides neon signs have revealed
連れ去ってmidnight 血走ったredeyes
Sweep us away into midnight, bloodshot red eyes
よふかしのうた
A hymn for nightwalkers
なんせ俺達の夜は忙しい
You know, it’s gon’ be a busy night
keep on dancin さぁ鬼の居ぬ間に
and gotta keep on dancin’ c’mon while all the demons are away
俺達の夜は忙しい oh yeah
it’s gon’ be a busy night, oh yeah
なんせ俺達の夜は忙しい
You know, it’s gon’ be a busy night
keep on dancin さぁ鬼の居ぬ間に
and gotta keep on dancin’ c’mon while all the demons are away
俺達の夜は忙しい oh yeah
it’s gon’ be a busy night, oh yeah
ガキの頃から夜が好きだった
I’ve liked the night since I was a brat
9時に寝るのは何故か嫌だった
Hated to go to bed before nine
なんと無くただ勿体なかった
It just felt like such a waste
お前の事がもっと知りたかった
Wished I’d known more about you
いわゆる三文の得
Early riser, screw it
投げ売ってでも見たいのさもっと奥の奥の奥
Let me witness what’s deeper inside
色濃く紐解く
Unravel it to the very end
12オクロックから丑の刻まで
Late in the night, 12 to 2
初めてお前を跨いだのは確か14
The first time I strode across you...
俺は何も知らねえワナビィ
I’m just a wannabe, know nothing at all
手取り足取り全てが新しい
Every step, every move look like a brand-new thing
姿形にその香り
Your appearance and your smell
静けさが似合うその黒い肌に
Even silence would suit your dark skin
吸い込まれてた手招きされるままに
I was hooked on it as you lured me in
それからお前は音楽をくれた
And you gave me music
女の裸も見せてくれた
Showed me the naked skin
飲んだ事ねえ酒に口づけて
You let me take a sip of a drink I never had
オトンタバコくすね火をつけた
Steal my daddy’s cigarette and lit it
やってはいけないが溢れて
There’s a ton of things I mustn’t do
知っちゃいけないに塗れてる
There’s a ton of things I mustn’t know
迎えに来る闇に紛れて
Lurking in the dark, you’d pick me up
お前はいつも気まぐれで…
You’ve always been that kind of freak...
よふかしのうた
A hymn for nightwalkers
照らしってって moonlight
Let the moonlight shine on us
目を奪ってブルーライト
Let the blue light daze our eyes
ネオンサインが呼ぶ表裏
Two sides neon signs have revealed
よふかしのうた
A hymn for nightwalkers
連れ去って midnight
Sweep us away into midnight
血走って redeyes
Bloodshot red eyes
大人達の子守唄
This lullaby goes out to the adults
なんせ俺達の夜は忙しい
You know, it’s gon’ be a busy night
keep on dancin さぁ鬼の居ぬ間に
and gotta keep on dancin’ c’mon while all the demons are away
俺達の夜は忙しい oh yeah
it’s gon’ be a busy night, oh yeah
なんせ俺達の夜は忙しい
You know, it’s gon’ be a busy night
keep on dancin さぁ鬼の居ぬ間に
and gotta keep on dancin’ c’mon while all the demons are away
俺達の夜は忙しい oh yeah
it’s gon’ be a busy night, oh yeah
Minasan, welcome one and all to my very special Halloween night concert,
J-RAP in JIGOKU! I hope you guys are already having a great time.
The first song that I kicked off this concert with is 'Yofukashi no Uta' or in English, 'A Staying Up Late Lullaby' or something like that.
It's my favorite creepy-nuts song ever, and I actually got to perform it with Creepy Nuts a while back, but that was a paid thing, a paid programming.
So, uh this time, I got to perform it for you guys on this amazing stage!
Isn't it so awesome?
It- I feel like it really like encapsulates the idea of J-Rap, which is my roots, by the way.
The theme of this concert is 'roots', like where do you come from? And and you should never forget your roots. Well, my roots are in J-Rap, Japanese rap.
They always have been uh for many years, ever since I came here to Japan uh to be involved in the scene.
Isn't it an amazing stage? Look at it, we got graffiti everywhere! Oh my gosh, it's like...
nanka nihon no teisu mo haitteru kara, hontouni saikou!
It's got that Japanese taste to it too, it's truly the best!
meccha meccha ii kanji, kakkuii desu ne kono stage!
It feels so, so good, this stage is so cool!
sutechina butai no ue ni, ironna J-Rap kyoku yatte mitai to omoimasu.
On this wonderful stage, I wanted to try performing lots of different J-Rap songs.
And there's so many different kinds of J-Rap and different communities within the genre of J-Rap, and so I tried to pick a lot of songs for the setlist that I guess...
are like very different from each other, but still Japanese rap.
And um I think that you guys might also realize there's a bit of a story going on in between some of the songs, so I hope you guys will pay attention to that 'cause that's also about my roots.
Moving on to the hashtag, the hashtag is #JRAPinJIGOKU, like I said, #JRAPinJIGOKU. I hope you guys will take lots of screenshots! Screenshot o ippai totte hoshii onegai shimasu!
Moving on to the hashtag, the hashtag is #JRAPinJIGOKU, like I said, #JRAPinJIGOKU. I hope you guys will take lots of screenshots! Please take lots of screenshots, I beg you!
Hai! There's going to be a lot of really cool effects on the stage, like there's an audio spectrum on the ground...
that like it like reacts to my vocals when I'm singing and stuff like that.
It's just- it's really cool. This is a dream live for me, so I hope you guys will enjoy!
We also have a lot of really amazing guests, some that are gonna blow your mind.
Sugoi, tottemo sutekina gesuto mo kuru kara minasan mite kudasai! Korekara motto...
Amazing, some wonderful guests are coming too, so everyone please watch! From now on, even more...
Hade ni buchigamaseo zeeeii!
Let's blow it up in style, yeah!
Soudesune, kariote ppoi serifu. Uh yeah, this is kind of my my catchphrase these days.
That's right, a Calliope-esque line. Uh yeah, this is kind of my catchphrase these days.
Without further ado, let's move on to the next song, everyone please enjoy and keep the party going! Let's go!
愛しか感じたくもない
I don't want to feel anything but love,
もう何の分け隔えもない
with no discrimination left at all.
まとめてかかってきなさい
Come at me all at once,
今なら全て受け止めるから
because I'll accept everything right now.
で、一体何が欲しいわけ
So, what on earth do you even want?
誰に勝ちたいわけ
Who the heck are you trying to beat?
なかなか気づけんよね
It's hard to realize, isn't it,
何もかも既に持っているのにね
even when you already have everything?
花祭り 夏祭り
Flower festival, summer festival,
何でも好きに選びな
choose whatever you like.
秋祭り 冬休み
Autumn festival, winter break,
その閉じた心今ここ開けな
open up that closed heart right here and now.
祭り 祭り
Festival, festival,
毎日いとおしき何かの
every day is a beloved festival
祭り 祭り
of something special,
あれもこれもが大当たり
where this and that are both big hits.
比べるものはない
There's nothing to compare to,
勝ちや負けとか一切ない
no such thing as winning or losing.
何も知ったこっちゃない
I couldn't care less about any of it,
好きにしてください
do whatever you want.
何も知ったこっちゃない
I couldn't care less,
好きにしてください
do as you please.
僕が激しく泣いたせいで 君が派手に笑ったせいで
Because I cried so hard, because you laughed out loud,
夏の暑さ身体を焦がして 冬の厳しさ骨身に染みた
the summer heat burned our bodies, winter's harshness chilled us to the bone.
真っ平らに生きられたら 真っ直ぐにそこへ行けたかな
If I had lived evenly, could I have gone straight there?
っしゅあ 今なら遅くはねーから
Well, it's not too late now,
っしゅあ っしゅあ っしゅあ っしゅあ
so aight, aight, aight, aight!
花祭り 夏祭り
Flower festival, summer festival,
生まれゆくもの死にゆくもの 全てが同時期の出来事
things being born and dying, all happening at the same time.
秋祭り 冬休み
Autumn festival, winter break,
みな抱きしめたら踊りなさいな さいな
embrace it all and dance away, dance away!
祭り 祭り 毎日いとおしき何かの
Festival, festival, every day is some beloved festival,
祭り 祭り あれもこれもが有り難し
festival, festival, where this and that are precious.
苦しむことは何もない
There is nothing to suffer over,
肩落とすこと一切ない
no reason to hang your head at all.
祭り 祭り
Festival, festival,
毎日いとおしき何かの
every day is a beloved festival
祭り 祭り
of something special,
あれもこれもが有り難し
where this and that are so precious.
苦しむことは何もない
There is nothing to suffer over,
肩落とすこと一切ない
no reason to hang your head at all.
祭り 祭り
Festival, festival,
毎日いとおしき何かの
every day is a beloved festival
祭り 祭り
of something special,
何にせよめでたい
anyway, it's all worth celebrating!
Hey DJ カマセ yeah yeah yeah
Hey DJ, play it, yeah, yeah, yeah!
気分上々↑↑の
Feeling great up, up,
針落とせ 音鳴らせ パーリナイ
drop the needle, make some noise, party night!
飲もう ライライライ みんなで踊れ！
Let's drink, right, right, right, everybody dance!
hip-pop ピーポー かけてよ ミラクル number
Hip-pop people, play that miracle number!
Yo! こんな時代に分かち合う music
Yo! Music to share in times like these,
探したくて回す地球儀
spinning the globe to find it.
ぐらつく不安定生活 それだからバランス重視
Unstable lives make balance important,
良いことばかりじゃないから「頑張れる！」
it's not all good times, so we can keep trying!
最悪な日にキック
Give that worst day a kick,
再起動のボタンクリック！
hit the restart button - click!
DJかけて！！今trip
DJ, play it!! Now trip,
しゃれてるビートに乗っけて感じて体揺そうよ
feel the stylish beat and rock your body.
Hey DJ カマセ yeah yeah yeah
Hey DJ, play it, yeah, yeah, yeah,
気分上々↑↑の
feeling great up, up,
針落とせ 音鳴らせ パーリナイ
drop the needle, make some noise, party night!
飲もう ライライライ みんなで踊れ！
Let's drink, right, right, right, everybody dance!
みんなで踊れ！
Everyone, dance!
hip-pop ピーポー
Hip-pop people,
かけてよ ミラクル number
play that miracle number!
Hey DJ カマセ yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey DJ, play it, yeah, yeah, yeah,
気分上々↑↑の
feeling high,
針落とせ 音鳴らせ パーリナイ
drop the needle, make some noise, party night!
飲もう ライライライ
Let's drink, right, right, right,
みんなで踊れ！
everybody dance!
hip-pop ピーポー
Hip-pop people,
かけてよ ミラクル number
play that miracle number!
Yo! こんな時代に
Yo! In times like these,
分かり合う music
we share our music,
探したくて 回す地球儀
spinning the globe in search.
グラつく 不安定 生活 それだから バランス重視
Faltering in our unstable lives, balance is key.
良い こと ばかり じゃ ない から 「頑張れる!」
It's not all good times, so we can keep trying!
最悪 な 日 に キック
Give that horrible day a kick,
再起動 の ボタン クリック!
press the restart button—click!
DJ かけて!! 今 trip
DJ, play it! Now trip,
シャレてる ビート に 乗って 感じる 体 揺らそうよ
feel the stylish beat and rock your body!
Hey DJ カマセ
Hey DJ, play it,
yeah, yeah, yeah
気分上々↑↑の
feeling high,
針落とせ 音鳴らせ パーリナイ
drop the needle, make some noise, party night!
飲もう ライライライ
Let's drink, right, right, right,
みんなで踊れ！
everybody dance!
hip-pop ピーポー
Hip-pop people,
かけてよ ミラクル number
play that miracle number!
hip hop, r & b, pops, techno, house, rock...
Hip hop, R&B, pop, techno, house, rock...
hip pop!!
オリジナル 探す キーポイント
The key point is searching for originality,
それぞれの 色 重ね合わせる レインボー
overlapping colors to make a rainbow.
君に聴かせ たいが為 苦しむ挙句の果て
After all the suffering just to let you hear it...
十字固め
Cross armlock,
今を楽しみたいんだね
I just want to have fun now!
let's hip pop!! here we, here we go!!
はしゃぐ フロア の 上
Playing on the floor,
頭中 ゆさゆさる
shaking your brain.
Hey DJ シャシャれ
Hey DJ, keep it simple,
yeah, yeah, yeah
気分上々↑↑の
feeling high,
波に乗って 弾け飛べ ファンキーナイ
ride the wave, bursting, jumping, funky night!
飲もう ライライライ
Let's drink, right, right, right,
みんなで踊れ！
everybody dance!
hip-pop ピーポー 朝まで ミラクル number
Hip-pop people, miracle number all night long!
ミラーボール スモーク の におい
Mirrorball, the smell of smoke,
溶けるような ハーモニー
a harmony that'll make you melt,
身にまとって 踊り明かす がむしゃらなままで
wrap it around you and dance the night away recklessly.
Hey DJ カマセ yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey DJ, play it, yeah, yeah, yeah,
気分上々↑↑の
feeling high,
針落とせ 音鳴らせ パーリナイ
drop the needle, make some noise, party night!
飲もう ライライライ
Let's drink, right, right, right,
みんなで踊れ！
everybody dance!
hip-pop ピーポー かけてよ ミラクル number
Hip-pop people, play that miracle number!
Hey DJ カマセ yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey DJ, play it, yeah, yeah, yeah,
気分上々↑↑の
feeling high,
針落とせ 音鳴らせ パーリナイ
drop the needle, make some noise, party night!
飲もう ライライライ
Let's drink, right, right, right,
みんなで踊れ！
everybody dance!
hip-pop ピーポー かけてよ ミラクル number
Hip-pop people, play that miracle number!
Hey DJ カマセ yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey DJ, play it, yeah, yeah, yeah,
気分上々↑↑の
feeling high,
みんなで踊れ！
everybody dance!
Pop, pop, pop, pop! Mirrorball!
How'd you guys think of our performance?
My turn! Pop, pop!
My biggest bow-bow!
Oh my gosh!
Thank you so much! It's hard to hold back the bow-bows.
You see, both of you are here, it's like I'm being overwhelmed.
Seeing both of you here, it's like I'm being overwhelmed.
But I'm so happy to have both of you here. Thank you so much!
And for those that don't know...
Jiko shoukai onegaishimasu!
Please introduce yourselves!
I love you-wawa! I love you-wawa!
I love you-woco! I love you-woco!
I love you too, Mori-chan!
Together we're Fuwawa Abyssgard!
And I'm Mori Calliope!
Yay, that was so fun! Thank you so much, you guys!
I love dancing with you guys and learning the dance together and our singing and this move...
And then the robot! It was so cool! I'll never forget it.
I have so many unforgettable experiences with you guys, like when we went to the onsen...
We had a bit of mishaps. There was a mishap, there was a misunderstanding...
Yeah, everybody went into the kakumizu because I thought it was the cold pool.
There was no sign that said 'Don't come in here'.
No sign! It didn't say nothing! It was kakumizu, you can pour the water...
So you just thought it was like a small bath, but oh, it's a cold bath!
Hajaranai ne. Hajaranai... そんなはずじゃなかったのねって。
Hajaranai ne. Hajaranai... "That's not how it was supposed to be," you know.
We didn't know the misunderstanding, but it's okay, it's a good memory, yes so.
Ah, I feel like we need to hit the onsen after this. Right after, right after the show!
For now, I'm doing this big show, sending around Dera! Wow.
I want to know, what are you guys' roots?
Roots like idols and anime songs... that's an idol root!
That's right! Stacking those nodes!
There could have been no one better to perform this song with, so...
Thank you so much! It was so fun, you guys!
Let's hang out again soon and do it together, okay?
Can I get a hug?
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
See you!
The loudest bow-wows ever.
Well, I'm feeling very energized.
Those two are the best, and honestly, I feel ready to talk about the next part of my roots.
I hope you guys will enjoy the story as it's unfolding, kind of like my life.
I don't know. Are you guys ready for the next part?
Let's keep enjoying the show together, and, um, and yeah, please enjoy.
Douso!
The days I can't get back...
Days we spent singing and laughing and not caring.
There was peace in that hectic time.
Maybe someday I can go on a musical adventure with my friends, too! Just like those performers I admire so much.
But...
I was already on one.
I just didn't see it.
Night after night, in a strange country full of words I didn't understand, unfamiliar things were everywhere and yet...
They became irreplaceable.
So then... how were any of us to know?
It wasn't meant to last.
Don't suppose that's where all the trouble began...?
Lyrics: らうびと, ill bell / Music: らうびと, D.watt
Thank you so much!
Let's do this! Come on, Reine, here we go!
1, 2, 3, 4, 行くぞ、ショー開始 bitとbell混ぜる
1, 2, 3, 4, Let's go, show starting, bit and bell mixed in
このrapまたと無い絶頂を絶対にオーガナイズ
This rap is second to none, absolutely to be organized
1 & 2 ロック ザ マイク スタートライン
1 & 2 Lock the mic, starting line
「邪険にするなよ ここで遊ぼうぜ」だって俺ら地球レペゼン
"Don't go to evil places, let's play here," that's what our Earth level base says
とうに音に飛び込んできたんだよ 当人とっても楽しいんだもん!!!!!
We've already flown into the sound, and as the people involved, it's so much fun!!!!!
ガチで勝負だぜ very scandalous!! 各々マイク手に掴んだら
It's a serious showdown, very scandalous!! Once each holds the mic in hand,
真剣さのみ振るいたい "show must go on"
only true seriousness wants to be swung, "show must go on"
シーケンサからブッ放され 一生増す轟音
Blasted from the sequence, ever-increasing roaring sound
(alright) you'd better open the door
(all day, all night) get ready, enter the floor
全部背負ったまま降りろ 今を撃ち抜くための弾丸をリロード
Carrying everything on our backs, let's descend to shoot through the present, reloading bullets
俺らオーディエンス沸かすだけ 音に乗っていくローテック皿回せ
We just hype the audience, spinning the rotary plates riding the beat
オーディエンス沸かせた程度の能力 ばら撒くこの宇宙に
The ability to make the audience go wild, scattering across this universe
「少しでも明日へ」だろ歩こう アンコールの向こうへと
"Toward tomorrow, even just a little." Let's walk, onward to the encore
誘う、君と次の街へ
Inviting you to the next town, with you
回り出したミラーボール 今宵、春夏秋冬ひとっ飛び
The mirror ball starts spinning, tonight, spring, summer, autumn, winter, each and every one
輪になって sing a song 地球儀を回せ！
Gather in a circle and sing a song, spin the globe!
高級車、プール付きの大邸宅 または四六時中抱いていたようなハニーと一大計画
A luxury car, a mansion with a pool, or perhaps embracing honey twenty-four seven
末広の大形描く
drawing big outlines of far-reaching expansion
いつか光差すまで
Until the light shines through...
「さあ、行こう」
"Now then, let's go."
割れた鏡に 映した影は
Shadows reflected in a shattered mirror
薄明かり遮り
blocking the twilight.
手のひらにそっと 触れる欠片が 見せた牙痛みを知った
I knew the toothache shown by the fragment gently touched in my palm.
Reason 響いた心音
Reason, a resounding heartbeat,
Beast of prey
怪物の目覚めが本物
the monster's awakening is the real deal.
決める時だ
It's time to decide.
さあ 感情を打ち鳴らせ (Go ahead)
Now, let your emotions ring out (Go ahead),
全てを解き放って (Never end)
Unleash everything (Never end).
待ち受ける未来 傷だらけになったって
Even if the future awaiting us becomes battered,
構わない 進んで行こう
it doesn't matter, let's move forward.
争いの跡に 残るのは何
What remains in the wake of the conflict?
答えはまだ聞こえない
The answer cannot be heard yet.
涙はとうに 忘れたモノと 思っていた 頬を拭った
Thinking tears were something I'd forgotten long ago,
頬を拭った
I wiped my cheek.
Soldier 灰色の空
Soldier, the gray sky.
I've been here
呼び声は 自分自身だろう
The call must be my own.
逃れられない ずっと
I can't escape, always.
もういくつ 越えてきたんだろう
How many times must I have crossed over it,
交差する黒煙の中で
amidst the intersecting black smoke?
雲の切れ間を 見上げて探す 何を求めて
Looking up through the breaks in the clouds to search for what I'm seeking,
I will, fighting alone
消えない意志を燃やせ (Go ahead)
Burn an undying will (Go ahead),
背負った夢を果せ (Never end)
fulfill the dreams you carry on your back (Never end).
言い聞かせるように 握った小さな拳 掲げて 高々高く
Raise high, high up the small fist you clenched as if to lecture yourself.
さあ 感情を打ち鳴らせ (Go ahead)
Now, let your emotions ring out (Go ahead),
その目に火を灯せ (Never end)
light a fire in those eyes (Never end).
辿り着いた未来 傷だらけになったって
Even if the future we've reached is battered,
ここにいる 戦った証と とともに行こう Burn ash
let's go together with the proof that we fought here, Burn ash.
We are...
さあ堂々と通りです
Now, proudly step forward,
音と言葉を侍らせ
with sound and words as your retinue.
そこ退け男どもさ さながらモーズェ
Step aside, you men, like a tempest.
こちら東天 呑口女の意のままに進む OK
We're heading East, following the sovereign's will, OK?
サービスにつけられるハンディご覧遊ばせ
Check out the handy perks for our services.
これが私のマニフェストばり
This is my manifesto,
頭が高いですね 敵にもなれない
keep your chin up, you're not even our match.
噛み付くの同じいらないビーフ
Chomping on useless beef,
気安く呼んでんないよ無花果
don't call us so casually, you barren fruit.
Bad Queensの罠にハマれ
Falling into the trap of the Bad Queens,
上がるしか無い支持率
our approval rating can only go up.
Lipsから音韻まで固め
Solidify everything from your lips to your rhyme scheme,
ほらTopしか似合わんこの運命
see, only the top suits this destiny.
足りん脳で覚えとけよ 名前 勘違い由小路
Realize it with your body and mind, a name? Misunderstood, petty path.
上げろ狼煙 おそろしい
Raise the signal fire, slowpokes.
SHUT UP SHUT UP そんなんじゃダメ 生ぬるい
SHUT UP SHUT UP, that won't cut it, raw.
借り物の言葉じゃ 飛べないでしょ
With borrowed words, you can't even fly.
さあ 感情を打ち鳴らせ (Go ahead)
Now, let your emotions ring out (Go ahead),
全てを解き放って (Never end)
Unleash everything (Never end).
待ち受ける未来 傷だらけになったって
Even if the future awaiting us becomes battered,
構わない 進んで行こう
it doesn't matter, let's move forward.
争いの跡に 残るのは何
What remains in the wake of the conflict?
答えはまだ聞こえない
The answer cannot be heard yet.
涙はとうに 忘れたモノと 思っていた 頬を拭った
Thinking tears were something I'd forgotten long ago,
頬を拭った
I wiped my cheek.
Soldier 灰色の空
Soldier, the gray sky.
I've been here
呼び声は 自分自身だろう
The call must be my own.
逃れられない ずっと
I can't escape, always.
もういくつ 越えてきたんだろう
How many times must I have crossed over it,
交差する黒煙の中で
amidst the intersecting black smoke?
雲の切れ間を 見上げて探す 何を求めて
Looking up through the breaks in the clouds to search for what I'm seeking,
I will, fighting alone
消えない意志を燃やせ (Go ahead)
Burn an undying will (Go ahead),
背負った夢を果せ (Never end)
fulfill the dreams you carry on your back (Never end).
言い聞かせるように 握った小さな拳 掲げて 高々高く
Raise high, high up the small fist you clenched as if to lecture yourself.
さあ 感情を打ち鳴らせ (Go ahead)
Now, let your emotions ring out (Go ahead),
その目に火を灯せ (Never end)
light a fire in those eyes (Never end).
辿り着いた未来 傷だらけになったって
Even if the future we've reached is battered,
ここにいる 戦った証と とともに行こう Burn ash
let's go together with the proof that we fought here, Burn ash.
We are...
みんな
Everyone...
本当にありがとう
thank you so much.
We are...
中王区 マイク片手に
Right in the center, mic in hand,
分かり易く警告Ah
making it clear with a warning, ah.
We are... Check it out.
We are言の葉党
We are the verbal party!
さあ堂々とお通りです
Now step right up, proudly making your way,
音と言葉を侍らせ
with sound and words as your entourage.
そこ退け男どもさ さながらモーズェ
Step aside, you men, like a tempest.
こちら東天 呑口女の意のままに進むOK
We're heading East, following the sovereign's will, OK?
サービスにつけられるハンディご覧遊ばせ
Check out the handy perks for our services.
これが私のマニフェストばり
This is my manifesto,
頭が高いですね 敵にもなれない
keep your chin up, you're not even our match.
噛み付くの同じいらないビーフ
Chomping on useless beef,
気安く呼んでんないよ無花果
don't call us so casually, you barren fruit.
Bad Queensの罠にハマれ
Falling into the trap of the Bad Queens,
上がるしか無い支持率
our approval rating can only go up.
Lipsから音韻まで固め
Solidify everything from your lips to your rhyme scheme,
ほらTopしか似合わんこの運命
see, only the top suits this destiny.
足りん脳で覚えとけよ名前勘違い由小路
Realize it with your body and mind, a name? Misunderstood, petty path.
上げろ狼煙おそろしい
Raise the signal fire, slowpokes.
SHUT UP SHUT UPそんなんじゃダメ生ぬるい
SHUT UP SHUT UP, that won't cut it, raw.
借り物の言葉じゃ飛べないでしょ
With borrowed words, you can't even fly.
ガラスの天井 ああ先の先の先
Shatter the glass ceiling,
もっと試したいこの己
let's go beyond.
バウンスレミバウンス痛快フェンスにだって狂気の賛辞鳴らすよ
Bounce, let me bounce, it's a frenzy.
迷子になって眠りな話迷い無しの様な時代に
Lost in a maze, like a dream in an era of confusion.
今日日聞こえる枠の話題こいつらがガチだぜラップの王道大体くらいマックスクライの最後列以外には全くの眼中にない
Even today, hearing the framework,
揺り動けるロッサを履きほっと消える外の音の一瞬すら気をつける
the real deal is taking over.
戦々恐々試合言葉はバッカバッカ
Hard-fought matches are just child's play, words are ba-ba-ba-barbaric!
やっぱクラインとラッパラップブームを芯で成功イントラッパートラップオディエンスはトラッタラッグ無問題アイドントラックラクション
Yeah, rap, rap, trap, trap, boom, making a success.
We are...
さあ堂々とお通りです
Now step right up, proudly making your way,
音と言葉を侍らせ
with sound and words as your entourage.
そこ退け男どもさ さながらモーズェ
Step aside, you men, like a tempest.
こちら東天 呑口女の意のままに進むOK
We're heading East, following the sovereign's will, OK?
サービスにつけられるハンディご覧遊ばせ
Check out the handy perks for our services.
これが私のマニフェストばり
This is my manifesto,
頭が高いですね 敵にもなれない
keep your chin up, you're not even our match.
噛み付くの同じいらないビーフ
Chomping on useless beef,
気安く呼んでんないよ無花果
don't call us so casually, you barren fruit.
Bad Queensの罠にハマれ
Falling into the trap of the Bad Queens,
上がるしか無い支持率
our approval rating can only go up.
Lipsから音韻まで固め
Solidify everything from your lips to your rhyme scheme,
ほらTopしか似合わんこの運命
see, only the top suits this destiny.
足りん脳で覚えとけよ名前勘違い由小路
Realize it with your body and mind, a name? Misunderstood, petty path.
上げろ狼煙おそろしい
Raise the signal fire, slowpokes.
SHUT UP SHUT UPそんなんじゃダメ生ぬるい
SHUT UP SHUT UP, that won't cut it, raw.
借り物の言葉じゃ飛べないでしょ
With borrowed words, you can't even fly.
Hands up hands up 今から素通りする電車
Hands up, hands up, the train is passing right through now.
ため息と共に 溢れる omg
Overflowing with sighs, oh my god,
もう息すらしねえ野次達はラッタッタ
the hecklers shouting without a breath are rattatta.
余裕かまして温存した前半戦の判断 ありゃ甘かった
Conserving energy in the first half was way too naive.
開いた差は簡単には埋まらねえし この状況を打開する策があるのかよ
The gap won't easily close. Is there a way to break through?
oh that's right 任せときな アイツが来るぜさあオライ
Oh that's right, leave it to me, here they come, alright!
yes! i'm back! 待たせたな
Yes! I'm back! Kept you waiting?
ヒット じゃ足りない？ チャンスはラスト？ ヒーローは遅れて暴れてなんぼ
A hit isn't enough? Last chance? Heroes arrive late and make a scene.
死亡フラグは逆転の発想 出来が違ってか
Death flags are reverse thinking. Is our output different,
見据える先 違えんだわ 来世までさらばホームランさ
Or what we're aiming at? Farewell till the afterlife, home run!
共闘さ let's get back 暴れ出すサイン 踵を返すなら お早めに
Fighting together, let's get back, the sign to go wild. Turn back soon.
捲りめく様な展開が 今始まるんだ let's get high 止まる気はない
A thrilling turn of events is starting right now. Let's get high, we won't stop.
手のひら返しなら お早めに な？ 僕らの想像を超えて ぶっ飛んでった so fast
Flip your script early. See? Flying past our imagination so fast.
スイング した魂 は1発限りのだ moving を決めたら戻らないぜ 振り出し
A swung soul is a one-shot deal. Once you move, no going back.
苦しい？ もう losing? いやブーイングも無視で
Struggling? Already losing? Ignoring all the boos,
うっせーうっせーうっせーわ
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
退路を断ち all bet する vibe
Cutting off retreat, the vibe is going all-in.
争う気しかないのさ trend
The only intent is to fight, that's the trend.
価値を上げるため 勝ち上がる
Climbing up to raise our value.
いざ 想像を絶する環境も 逆境も 上等だ
Environments and adversities beyond imagination? Bring it on!
共闘さ let's get back 暴れ出すサイン 見逃すなサイン
Fighting together, let's get back, the sign to go wild, don't miss it.
どんてん返しなら お墨付き
If it's a plot twist, it's guaranteed.
夢のような光景は 目をこじ開け見損なうな
Open your eyes wide to see this dreamlike scene.
let's get high 許されぬミス 裏をかく土壇場 おもてなし
Let's get high, unpardonable mistakes, hospitality in a tight spot.
棒に振りはしない フルスイングで ぶっ飛んでいけ so far
Never swinging blindly, full swing, flying so far away.
start again and again 次は君の番 ガデム 何度も歯噛みし続けた毎晩
Start again and again, it's your turn. God damn, biting my teeth every night.
ただ do or die って もうやっちまったわ
Just do or die, and now I've gone and done it.
なら go なら go なら go
Then go, then go, then go!
共闘さ let's get back 暴れ出すサイン 瞬き厳禁で
Fighting together, let's get back, the sign to go wild, don't blink!
さあ let's get back 暴れ出すサイン 踵を返すなら お早めに
Now let's get back, the sign to go wild. Turn back soon.
捲りめく様な展開が 今始まるんだ let's get high 止まる気はない
A thrilling turn of events is starting right now. Let's get high, we won't stop.
手のひら返しなら お早めに な？ 僕らの想像を超えて ぶっ飛んでった so fast
Flip your script early. See? Flying past our imagination so fast.
ぶっ飛んでいけ so far
Fly so far away!
共闘さ let's get back
Fighting together, let's get back,
暴れ出すサイン
the sign to go wild.
踵を返すなら お早めに
Turn back soon if you're smart.
捲りめく様な展開が 今始まるんだ
A thrilling turn of events starts now.
let's get high
止まる気はない
we won't stop.
手のひら返しなら お早めに
Flip your script early.
な？ 僕らの想像を超えて ぶっ飛んでった so fast
See? Flying past our imagination so fast.
スイング した魂 は1発限りのだ
A swung soul is a one-shot deal.
moving を決めたら戻らないぜ 振り出し
Once you move, no going back to square one.
苦しい？ もう losing? いやブーイングも無視で
Struggling? Already losing? Ignoring the boos,
うっせーうっせーうっせーわ
shut up, shut up, shut up!
退路を断ち all bet する vibe
Cutting off retreat, going all-in.
争う気しかないのさ trend
Only intent to fight, that's the trend.
価値を上げるため 勝ち上がる
Climbing up to raise our value.
いざ 想像を絶する環境も 逆境も 上等だ
Environments and adversities beyond imagination? Bring it on!
共闘さ let's get back 暴れ出すサイン 見逃すなサイン
Fighting together, let's get back, the sign to go wild, don't miss it.
どんてん返しなら お墨付き
If it's a plot twist, it's guaranteed.
夢のような光景は 目をこじ開け見損なうな
Open your eyes wide to see this dreamlike scene.
let's get high 許されぬミス 裏をかく土壇場 おもてなし
Let's get high, unpardonable mistakes, hospitality in a tight spot.
棒に振りはしない フルスイングで ぶっ飛んでいけ so far
Never swinging blindly, full swing, flying so far away.
start again and again 次は君の番
Start again and again, it's your turn.
ガデム 何度も歯噛みし続けた毎晩
God damn, biting my teeth every single night.
ただ do or die って
Just do or die,
もうやっちまったわ
and now I've gone and done it.
なら go なら go なら go
Then go, then go, then go!
共闘さ let's get back 暴れ出すサイン 瞬き厳禁で
Fighting together, let's get back, the sign to go wild, don't blink!
さあ let's get back 暴れ出すサイン 踵を返すなら お早めに
Now let's get back, the sign to go wild. Turn back soon.
捲りめく様な展開が 今始まるんだ let's get high 止まる気はない
A thrilling turn of events is starting right now. Let's get high, we won't stop.
手のひら返しなら お早めに な？ 僕らの想像を超えて ぶっ飛んでった so fast
Flip your script early. See? Flying past our imagination so fast.
ぶっ飛んでいけ so far
Fly so far away!
共闘さ let's get back
Fighting together, let's get back
暴れ出すサイン
The sign to go wild
踵を返すなら お早めに
Turn back soon if you're smart
捲りめく様な展開が 今始まるんだ
A thrilling turn of events starts now
let's get high 止まる気はない
Let's get high, we won't stop
手のひら返しなら お早めに
Flip your script early
な？ 僕らの想像を超えて ぶっ飛んでった so fast
See? Flying past our imagination so fast
スイング した魂 は1発限りのだ
A swung soul is a one-shot deal.
moving を決めたら戻らないぜ 振り出し
Once you move, no going back.
苦しい？ もう losing? いやブーイングも無視で
Struggling? Already losing? Ignoring all the boos,
うっせーうっせーうっせーわ
shut up, shut up, shut up!
退路を断ち all bet する vibe
Cutting off retreat, going all-in.
争う気しかないのさ trend
Only intent to fight, that's the trend.
価値を上げるため 勝ち上がる
Climbing up to raise our value.
いざ 想像を絶する環境も 逆境も 上等だ
Environments and adversities beyond imagination? Bring it on!
共闘さ let's get back 暴れ出すサイン 見逃すなサイン
Fighting together, let's get back, the sign to go wild, don't miss it.
どんてん返しなら お墨付き
If it's a plot twist, it's guaranteed.
夢のような光景は 目目をこじ開け見損なうな
Open your eyes wide to see this dreamlike scene.
let's get high 許されぬミス 裏をかく土壇場 おもてなし
Let's get high, unpardonable mistakes, hospitality in a tight spot.
棒に振りはしない フルスイングで ぶっ飛んでいけ so far
Never swinging blindly, full swing, flying so far away.
start again and again 次は君の番
Start again and again, it's your turn.
ガデム 何度も歯噛みし続けた毎晩
God damn, biting my teeth every single night.
ただ do or die って
Just do or die,
もうやっちまったわ
and now I've gone and done it.
なら go なら go なら go
Then go, then go, then go!
共闘さ let's get back 暴れ出すサイン 瞬き厳禁で
Fighting together, let's get back, the sign to go wild, don't blink!
さあ let's get back 暴れ出すサイン 踵を返すなら お早めに
Now let's get back, the sign to go wild. Turn back soon.
捲りめく様な展開が 今始まるんだ let's get high 止まる気はない
A thrilling turn of events is starting right now. Let's get high, we won't stop.
手のひら返しなら お早めに な？ 僕らの想像を超えて ぶっ飛んでった so fast
Flip your script early. See? Flying past our imagination so fast.
ぶっ飛んでいけ so far
Fly so far away!
Everybody, Bae's take off!
What's up? I am Chaos, the end of end! A steel-spun rat
trapped in a cage of ice, your best friend Bellz comes with a squeak!
That was dramatic.
In a good way. That was in a good way.
Calli!
Happy Halloween!
Welcome to J-Rap in Jigoku! Thank you so much for the two songs.
Yeah! Thank you so much for inviting me. I had so much fun!
What was that choreo, man? I don't know, what was that choreo?
The- the- this? Oh, the- this- and then the- this?
Yeah!
It was so much fun! That's way more than I'm used to.
But- but it was fun. I had to pull out all- I'm so proud of you.
You did so good. Thank you.
You did so good. I got to get my stamina back. I'm sick.
Listen, Bae, the- the theme of this whole deal is roots.
So, like, what are your roots? Like, what are you, like-
I don't know, I feel like there'll be an answer, but go ahead and answer anyway.
Well, I guess I started a love of music from a young age. I also love dance from a young age.
Yeah. What the heck? Fancy move! Fancy move! What the heck?
I guess I started to dance to live my roots.
I love performing, and I hope to continue to be able to perform for everyone who wants to watch.
Yeah! Yeah! Heck yeah!
You know, Bae actually had a show recently, so go check it out, join it. Check it out on her channel!
It's really really awesome. My goodness, I nearly- that- that was the end. I nearly-
I nearly- everything was ended off.
Oh, my goodness! I feel you, seriously.
Well, thank you so much for coming today, Bae. Let's hang out again.
Yes! So much! Yeah, I want to hang out again.
Let's do it! Whether it be, you know, dancing, yeah, or otherwise. Oh, my god, she's good at it. Stop, stop!
That's awesome. All right, see you later, Bae!
Thank you again so much for having me. Thank you for having me.
Love the rest of the show. Bye-bye!
I guess we're going on to the next part of the show.
Next up, you're going to see a video that is part three, the finale of, I guess, some kind of like- I don't know-
movie about my roots. And after that, I've got something very special to share with you guys.
A special reveal of a brand new me. So I hope you guys will enjoy it. While you guys watch that, I'm going to go catch my breath.
Please keep enjoying J-Rap in Jigoku. Peace!
They shut it all down.
The miasma that permeated this town did its job, and the people I ran through those nights with...
just kind of... disappeared.
Back to real life.
They left the dream.
How am I supposed to go back?
This music is the only reason I'm here.
There's nothing left back there for me.
In a land where I lost my identity.
If there's no more music here, then I have no choice but to go home.
It was music that brought me to this country.
It was music that kept me here.
But... it was a hand that reached out at that moment that I thought I'd never hear an inspiring melody again.
Maybe it was never the end of a life.
It was the continuation of a story... My story.
That stage went dark, but ya know... You never really forget where you came from.
Illな legacy 違うエネルギー
Ill legacy, different energy,
病める民が求む この言葉がセラピー
lost humanity looking for my words of therapy.
Bad b***hのpedigree You're not a friend to me
Bad bitch pedigree, you're not a friend to me.
対等に話したいなら 登ってこいこのpyramid
If you wanna speak to me, then come up on this pyramid.
女神君臨 与えるダメージ
Goddess reigns, giving damages,
バース蹴ればspinning bird kicks まるでChung-Li
kicking verse with spinning bird kicks, just like Chung-Li.
Holy trinity Money power respect 全てを get
Holy trinity, money power respect, get everything.
なんて思い描き grind 働く 朝 昼 晩
Visualize and grind, working day and night.
next place 深夜 に 出番 悩み も 焦り も 全部
Next stage, late night show, stress and anxiety all
光 に 変え て みせる mステ 出 た から 何 ？
turned into light. So what if I'm on TV?
ヒット なきゃ 続き は 無い
If I don't get hits, there's no next.
ヒット 、 ヒット 、 知ら ない 人 に も 言わ れる お前 は 誰
Hits, hits, even strangers ask who you are.
「 姉さん なら もっと イケる 」
"You can go way further, big sis."
あの 日 yzerr が 言っ て くれ た
YZERR told me that day.
ill な legacy
ill legacy
違う エナジー
different energy,
病める 民 が 求む
sickly people searching for
この 言葉 が セラピー
these words as therapy,
bad bitch の pedigree
a bad bitch pedigree.
you 're not a friend to me
You're not a friend to me.
対等 に 話し たい なら 登っ て こい この pyramid
If you want to talk on equal terms, climb this pyramid!
女神 君 臨
The goddess reigns,
与える ダメージ
dealing damage,
バーズ 蹴り ば spinning bird kicks
kicking verses with spinning bird kicks,
まるで chung - li
just like Chun-Li.
holy trinity
money power respect 全て を get
money, power, respect, get everything.
なんて 思い描き grind
Visualize and grind,
働く 朝 昼 晩
working day and night.
next place 深夜 に 出番
Next stage, right to the stage.
悩み も 焦り も 全部 光 に 変え て みせる
Stress, anxiety, and all that will be turned into light!
mステ 出 た から 何 ？
So what if I'm on TV?
ヒット なかりゃ 続き は 無い
If I don't make hits, there's no continuation.
ヒット 、 ヒット 、 知ら ない 人 に も 言わ れる お前 は 誰
Hits, hits, even strangers asking, "Who are you?"
「 姉さん なら もっと イケル 」
"You could do way better, sis,"
あの 日 yzerr が 言っ て くれ た
YZERR told me that day.
天国 から 見守っ て いる
Watching over me from heaven,
死ぬ 前 の あいつ も 言っ て い た
the same thing he said before he died.
逃げ られ ない 今更
There's no running away now,
随所 に 仕掛ける 罠
setting traps everywhere.
gimme gucci pucci and dem prada
急い で 来 て ハバハバ
hurry up and come, hubba hubba.
i don't got time to play with you
とよみ も 金 が かかる
Raising toyomi costs money too.
耳 を かっぽじっ て 聞き な
Clean your dirty ears and listen up,
耳 揃え て すぐ に pay up
have it all aligned and pay up!
gila gila
gin gin gila
ice on ice on killa
jala jala
million dollars
ice on ice on killa
gila gila
gin gin gila
ice on ice on killa
haters お疲れ様
Good job, haters,
work hard , play harder
work hard, play harder!
首元 なら キラキラ
Glittering around my neckline,
混ざり 気 ない 純度 100 % の vv の chain
a 100% pure, unadulterated VV chain.
足元 から ほらほら
Look at my feet, hey hey,
違い が わかる この 立ち 方 靴 なら レア
striking a pose, these rare shoes.
俺 達 いつも
We are always...
ヒット ヒット ヒット ずっと lit
Hit, hit, hit, forever lit,
きっと haters 達 ずっと 嫉妬
while haters will probably be forever jealous.
一歩 一歩 ずっと runnin 出す shit
Step by step, keep runnin' this shit.
dude 一緒 俺 なら sicko 今日 も
Dude, I'm a sicko too, always,
awich に 呼ばれりゃ 出 ない 訳 ない ready set
Never missing an invite from Awich, ready set.
alex に オーダー し て 作っ て もらっ てる この drip
Order-made drip crafted by Alex.
いくら 稼い で も 足り ない の yen
No matter how much I earn, it's never enough yen.
やりたい 事 に bet bet bet 投資 し て は 稼ぐ
Bet, bet, bet on what I want to do, invest and hustle,
から 倍 に しなきゃ do my thing
gotta double it to do my thing.
夜中 に ちょっと 相談 そっち の 方 調子 は どう
Late-night consultation, how's it going on your end?
atlanta の yzerr に 電話
Calling YZERR in Atlanta,
icebox で buss down 良い ね 俺 も 速攻 で 行く わ
buss down in the icebox, nice, I'll go right away.
有言 実行 っす no cap 1000 %
Walk the talk, no cap 1000%!
やりたい 事 が 言っ て たら たまたま 重なっ たり
Things I wanted to say overlapping by chance,
この 3 人 なら たちまち バズ っ たり
the three of us creating an instant buzz.
欲しい 物 なら 手 に 入れる 片端
Getting my hands on whatever I desire,
馬鹿 に し て た 奴ら は 赤っ恥
while those who laughed at us look like fools.
出 始め から 右肩 上がり
On the upward trend since day one,
まだ 気付い て ない よう な 奴 ばかり
though many still don't even realize it.
音 の 上 で 俺 生意気 ざかり
Being cheeky right over the beats,
俺 乗っけ てる 波 の 上
I'm riding the wave,
ヤレル 事 制限 は ねえ
there are no limits to what I can do.
この 口 で 稼ぐ yen
Making yen with this mouth of mine,
中々 こう も上手くいかない と 思う
it might not always go smoothly,
だけど real life
but in real life,
稼ぐ 額 増やす ぜ 去年 の 倍
I'm doubling my earnings from last year.
gila gila
gin gin gila
ice on ice on killa
jala jala
million dollars
ice on ice on killa
gila gila
gin gin gila
ice on ice on killa
haters お疲れ様
Good job, haters,
work hard , play harder
work hard, play harder!
ghetto town から 一 抜け し た
Escaped out of the ghetto town,
川崎 生まれ の b boy だっけ なら
a B-boy born in Kawasaki,
bad boy から なる billionaire
a bad boy turning into a billionaire.
口座 に 積ん でる 今 9 桁
Now stacking 9 digits in my bank account.
ギラギラ で あいつ は ジェラス
They're jealous of my flashiness,
嫌な 奴ら が 狙う
haters are aiming for me.
ダラダラ し て たら 馬鹿
You're a fool if you slack off,
magic city で ばらまく dollar
scattering dollars in Magic City.
可愛い あの 子 も こっち 来 て
Pretty girls come over here,
ソファ に ゆっくり 腰掛け て は
relaxing on the couch
ルイ ・ ロデール の 古酒 シャンパン
with vintage Louis Roederer champagne.
会計 男気 また じゃんけん
When the bill comes, we play rock-paper-scissors like men.
今 は 好きな 物 チョイス し てる から
Now I'm choosing whatever I want,
未来 の ビジネス 投資 し てる
investing in future businesses.
jewelry に 全て を 使い 切っ ちまっ たら
If I spent everything on jewelry,
寒 すぎ 今頃 凍死 し てる
I'd be freezing to death right about now.
全国 規模 と 上っく 精度
Nationwide scale and high precision,
見つめる エイム は 高 精度
my aimed vision is top-tier.
ここ まで き た 博打 と 才能
Gambling and talent got me this far,
闇 の 中 で 振る サイコロ
rolling the dice in the darkness.
後 先 より 全額 ベッド
Betting it all instead of looking ahead,
当て れ ば 一 日 に し て 天国
if you hit, it's paradise overnight,
それ か 一人 凍える 監獄
or else a solitary freezing cell.
夢 から 覚め 今 から 交渉
Waking from the dream, now for negotiations,
数 億円 する 相談
consultations worth hundreds of millions of yen.
fujiwara hiroshi の 履い て いる jordan
Jordan sneakers worn by Hiroshi Fujiwara,
お前 じゃ 笑え ねえ 俺 ら の 冗談
you can't laugh at our jokes.
痛く も 痒く も ねえ 楽勝 じゃん
It doesn't hurt or itch, piece of cake,
0 から 手 に し た 二つ の 賞賛
two accolades earned from zero.
あいつ の ヘイト も お金 と 交換
Exchanging haters' hate for money,
時計 が 差し てる 天辺 と 王冠
the clock pointing at the zenith and crown.
お前 と の 間 に 線 引く border
Drawing a border between you and me,
tsunami wavy 街 に 降らす yen
raining yen upon the tsunami wavy streets.
まるで ピカチュウ ピカピカ 過ぎ 痺れ させる チェーン
Like Pikachu, gleaming and dazzlingly paralyzing chains.
gila gila
gin gin gila
ice on ice on killa
jala jala
million dollars
ice on ice on killa
gila gila
gin gin gila
ice on ice on killa
haters お疲れ様
Good job, haters,
work hard , play harder
work hard, play harder!
ゲットー から 抜け出し た
Escaped out of the ghetto,
川崎 生まれ の b boy
a Kawasaki-born B-boy,
bad boy から なる billionaire
a bad boy turning into a billionaire.
口座 に 積ん でる 今 9 桁
Now with 9 digits stacked in my account,
ギラギラ で あいつ は ジェラス
others are jealous of my flashiness.
嫌な 奴ら が 狙う
Haters are coming after me,
ダラダラ し て たら 馬鹿
you're a fool if you slack off.
magic city で ばらまく dollar
Scattering dollars in Magic City,
可愛い あの 子 も こっち 来 て
pretty girls come over here,
ソファ に ゆっくり 腰掛け て は
relaxing on the couch
ルイ ・ ロデール の 古酒 シャンパン
with vintage Louis Roederer champagne.
会計 男気 また じゃんけん
When the bill comes, we play rock-paper-scissors like men.
今 は 好きな 物 チョイス し てる から
Now I'm choosing whatever I like,
未来 の ビジネス 投資 し てる
investing in future businesses.
jewelry に 全て を 使い 切っ ちまっ たら
If I spent everything on jewelry,
寒 すぎ 今頃 凍死 し てる
I'd be freezing to death right about now.
全国 規模 と 上っく 精度
Nationwide scale and high precision,
見つめる エイム は 高 精度
my aimed vision is top-tier.
ここ まで き た 博打 と 才能
Gambling and talent got me this far,
闇 の 中 で 振る サイコロ
rolling the dice in the darkness.
後 先 より 全額 ベッド
Betting it all instead of looking ahead,
当て れ ば 一 日 に し て 天国
if you hit, it's paradise overnight,
それ か 一人 凍える 監獄
or else a solitary freezing cell.
夢 から 覚め 今 から 交渉
Waking from the dream, now for negotiations,
数 億円 する 相談
consultations worth hundreds of millions of yen.
fujiwara hiroshi の 履い て いる jordan
Jordan sneakers worn by Hiroshi Fujiwara,
お前 じゃ 笑え ねえ 俺 ら の 冗談
you guys can't laugh at our jokes.
痛く も 痒く も ねえ 楽勝 じゃん
It doesn't hurt or itch, piece of cake,
0 から 手 に し た 二つ の 賞賛
two accolades earned from zero.
あいつ の ヘイト も お金 と 交換
Exchanging haters' hate for money,
時計 が 差し てる 天辺 と 王冠
the clock pointing at the zenith and crown.
お前 と の 間 に 線 引く border
Drawing a border between you and me,
tsunami wavy 街 に 降らす yen
raining yen upon the tsunami wavy streets.
まるで ピカチュウ ピカピカ 過ぎ 痺れ させる チェーン
Like Pikachu, gleaming and dazzlingly paralyzing chains.
gila gila
gin gin gila
ice on ice on killa
jala jala
million dollars
ice on ice on killa
gila gila
gin gin gila
ice on ice on killa
haters お疲れ様
Good job, haters,
work hard , play harder
work hard, play harder!
皆さん！
Everyone!
What do you guys think?
We did it. The powers-that-be have finally gave me a brushed-up version of me,
We did it. The powers-that-be have finally given me a brushed-up version of me,
a brand new form. What do you think?
I wanted to reveal it in like a really exciting way.
I wanted to reveal it in a really exciting way.
So, I decided, uh, let's do it up here at the top of the castle.
こんな素敵な城
Such a wonderful castle...
で、めっちゃくちゃ中かっこいい。だからめちゃめちゃいい景色だからここで歌ってみたいなーって思いました。
And the inside is super cool. The view is amazing, so I thought I'd love to sing here.
I thought maybe I would sing here at the top of the castle to reveal this brand new, it's not an outfit, it's a new body.
I thought maybe I would sing here at the top of the castle to reveal this brand new—it's not an outfit, it's basically a new body.
And this is what I'll be using from now on, this version of me. So I hope you guys enjoy it.
And this is what I'll be using from now on, this version of me. So I hope that you guys enjoy it.
I'll probably go into more detail about it and show you during the members-only stream!
I'll probably go into more detail about it and show you in more detail during the members-only stream!
That's right, we are doing one of those, and everyone is welcome if you're a member.
So, please be sure to join membership, okay? And you might get a chance to see the old me again pretty soon here.
I get a feeling that, you know, we haven't fully closed out that chapter well, so we got to do that, right?
I get a feeling that we haven't fully closed out that chapter well, so we got to do that, right?
I don't know, it's very shiny
and oshare.
and stylish.
So, I hope that you guys liked that maybe a little overdone reveal.
Um, but yeah...
Witness, witness the power of the cooler!
Calliope Mori!
I'm still a little... I'm still a little lame though.
Sorry about that.
I can't really fix that.
But for now, let's keep enjoying J-RAP together, okay? Keep your eyes peeled, and...
sotsugyou ikimasu! Let's go!
DJ, play that music louder, お願い
DJ, play that music louder, please
二人でいるのに I miss you
Even though we're together, I miss you
近くにいても boy I miss you
Even when you're close by, boy, I miss you
少しだけ baby
Just a little bit, baby
(the cold crush lover is here)
もしかして maybe
Could it be, maybe
(the 流星's flowin' this year)
(the shooting star's flowin' this year)
気が変わる前に rock with you
Before your mind changes, rock with you
そして今日もこのまま with you
And today too, just like this, with you
どこまで(もう)少しだけ そして朝まで…
How far? Just a little more, and until morning...
(Uh in this atmosphere)
Don't know why this love gotta be むずかしい
Don't know why this love gotta be so hard
I'm 宇宙のSuper lover バーバルなのに
I'm space's super lover, even though I'm verbal
Don't know why this タカハシタカヒコのbeat
Don't know why this Takahashi Takahiko beat
Gotta be so fly with 領平とmelody... Now listen
Gotta be so fly with Ryohei and melody... Now listen
I don't know why 君の基準は とてもhigh
I don't know why your standards are so high
何もかも so uptight
Everything is so uptight
あれもこれもプレゼントされても
No matter what kind of presents are given
Baby don't you know それだけじゃないよ
Baby don't you know, that's not all
I don't know why すき間のない 迷いのない 態度 is that プライド?
I don't know why, that unyielding, unwavering attitude, is that pride?
cash or card 金で買えるもの何でも与えても she always says no
Cash or card, no matter what money can buy, she always says no
I gave her this, I gave her that 掲げられるものは夢のようだけど diamond rings are not forever
I gave her this, I gave her that, what's held up feels like a dream, but diamond rings are not forever
name anything, 宇宙船 that blings, just anything 月の光までも
Name anything, spaceships that bling, just anything up to the moonlight
baby come close to me
Ooh, baby can't you see
わかってほしい this is my 気持ち
I want you to understand, this is how I feel
Ooh tell me, tell me cuz 限度なんてない
Ooh tell me, tell me cuz there are no limits
好きなものbuy して la la la la la la
Buy whatever you like la la la la la la
Ooh, you say that you miss me
but call もないし
but you don't even call
じゃあどうして欲しい girl
Then what do you want me to do, girl?
Ooh, 教えてso I can do it right
Ooh, tell me so I can do it right
so tonight, you and I can just uh uh
DJ, play that music louder, お願い
DJ, play that music louder, please
Ooh How You Like Me Now, 2013年スタイル? m-flo's lovin' us now
Ooh How You Like Me Now, 2013 style? m-flo's lovin' us now
La La 聞こえてきたら Come and get me
When you hear La La, come and get me
No, cuz this ain't no joke, you deserve it all, and i'm treating you right, girl!
The way i'm livin' is 5 stars, sugoku large
chou mirai, kougokitai girl, you my type...
what's your namae?
tomaranai pull over!
throw ya, hands up in the air, kono ban
girl, nagareboshi mita youna feelin' de uh
sono hitomi ni hamatte taze, itsu no ma ni ka because
i'm bound to wreck your body and say turn the party out
tell me why doushite sure chigatte iku no?
(why don't we kiss no more?)
mou itsu no ma ni ka futari wa
(so far apart, tell me)
dou sureba ii no baby girl?
(uh, how you feelin' me now?)
we should be vibin' forever
One, 今日も金曜日で, we stay in love
One, today's Friday too, we stay in love
I got a lot of it, my dynamite, takahashi has love, keep you warm all night
どうしたらいいのでしょう Cafe Mocha hot hot
What should I do? Cafe Mocha hot hot
誰もが触れてみて jealousy とケチなざいぜつ
Everyone tries to touch, jealousy and petty stinginess
She killin' me, la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
mass mass like Stevie Wonder steel delivery
好きなこと do it baby, 櫛べに, ルテ, can weまじめに二人で rock rock if you don't mind
Do what you like baby, red comb, lute, can we earnestly rock rock together if you don't mind
お台場デート this is all about 今抜け出せないもの
Odaiba date, this is all about something we can't escape now
like a larva dayo all the time
それじゃ微笑んで hear your melody
Then smile and hear your melody
la la la la la la how can I can I touch it ever if
you spent some time with me, you can get nasty please
もしも二人になれたら gotta be loving and huggin' it up
If the two of us could be together, gotta be loving and huggin' it up
二人でいるのに 近くにいても
Even though we're together, even when you're close by
どこまで(もう)少しだけ そして朝まで
How far? Just a little more, and until morning
Uh in this atmosphere
Don't know why this love gotta be むずかしい
Don't know why this love gotta be so hard
I'm 宇宙のSuper lover バーバルなのに
I'm space's super lover, even though I'm verbal
Don't know why this タカハシタカヒコのbeat
Don't know why this Takahashi Takahiko beat
Gotta be so fly with 領平とmelody...
Gotta be so fly with Ryohei and melody...
Now listen, I don't know why 君の基準は とてもhigh
Now listen, I don't know why your standards are so high
何もかも so uptight...
Everything is so uptight...
DJ, play that music louder, お願い
DJ, play that music louder, please
Ooh How You Like Me Now, 2013年スタイル? m-flo's lovin' us now
Ooh How You Like Me Now, 2013 style? m-flo's lovin' us now
La La 聞こえてきたら Come and get me
When you hear La La, come and get me
No, cuz this ain't no joke, you deserve it all, and i'm treating you right, girl!
The way i'm livin' is 5 stars, sugoku large
chou mirai, kougokitai girl, you my type...
what's your namae?
tomaranai pull over!
throw ya, hands up in the air, kono ban
girl, nagareboshi mita youna feelin' de uh
sono hitomi ni hamatte taze, itsu no ma ni ka because
i'm bound to wreck your body and say turn the party out
tell me why doushite sure chigatte iku no?
(why don't we kiss no more?)
mou itsu no ma ni ka futari wa
(so far apart, tell me)
dou sureba ii no baby girl?
(uh, how you feelin' me now?)
I'm bound to wreck your body and say turn the party out
それはいったいどうしてすれ違っているの
Why in the world are we passing each other by?
(why can't we kiss no more?)
もういつの間にか二人は
Before we knew it, the two of us
(so far apart, tell me)
どうすればいいの baby girl?
What should I do, baby girl?
(uh, how you feelin' me now?)
we should be vibin' forever
半端なら K.O.
If you're half-hearted, K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
If you want to be fluffy, go ahead
開演準備しちゃおうか
Let's get ready for the show
泣いてても笑ってても愛してね
Whether you cry or laugh, love me
ほら Say No 低音響かせろ
Come on, say no, let the bass boom!
なんだかなって つまんないこともあるでしょう
Sometimes things are just boring, aren't they?
ロンリー論理のノート ハンディ本気脱走
Lonely logic notebook, handy serious escape
やんなっちゃって泥に Bad ご法度だろうが
Fed up with the mud, bad, forbidden,
溺れて堕ちて そろそろいっか
drowning and falling, it's about time
もっと頑張って アガるまでもっと頑張って
Try harder, try harder until you get excited
繋がろうひとりよりふたり 増えたら安心 心配ないや
Let's connect, two is better than one, no worries
Alright 任せて Don't mind 波あり難題
Alright, leave it to me, don't mind the waves
みんなで乗っかきちまえれば 案外さくっと行っちいそうだな
If we all jump on board, it might go smoothly
半端なら K.O.
If you're half-hearted, K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
If you want to be fluffy, go ahead
開演準備しちゃおうか
Let's get ready for the show
泣いてても笑ってても愛してね
Whether you cry or laugh, love me
ほら Say No 低音響かせろ
Come on, say no, let the bass boom!
今宵は暗転パーティー
Tonight is a blackout party
Woah 踊りだせ 踊りだせ 孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Woah, dance, dance, loneliness is sterilized, sold out
Woah 痛みまで おシェアで ここらでバイバイ let go
Woah, share the pain, say goodbye here, let go
どんな劣等感だてて 即興の血小板で
No matter how inferior you feel,
抑え込んで 突っ込んで 仕舞い込んじゃうでしょ
with blood platelets of improvisation
Up and down なテンション ねぇまいっちいってんの相当
Up and down tension, you're really messed up
ドバッと噴き出すのは 本音の独り言
It bursts out like honest mutterings
「別に興味ない」
"I don't care."
「特に関係ない」
"It doesn't matter."
塞ぎ込んで 舌尖絶頂へ 合図を奏でて PrrPrrPrr
Closed off, play the signal, prr prr prr
ほら集まって夜行だ 鳴っていこうぜ
Gather for the night ride, let's sing
半端なら K.O.
If you're half-hearted, K.O.
Woah 踊りだせ 踊りだせ 孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Woah, dance, dance, full house
Woah 痛みまで おシェアで 今宵も暗転パーティーだ
Woah, share the pain, tonight's a blackout party
Woah またのお越しを きっと
Woah, see you again, for sure
Woah 次回までお元気で ここらでバイバイ let go
Woah, stay healthy until next time, let go
Baby, baby, baby, baby, baby
It's those unintelligent monsters, ain't it?
What are they thinking? Please explain it
Don't really need this crap, can't waste time
What I possess can't copy and paste, uh
I'm doing it better, never settling for another regular
I'm doing it better, never settling for a regular
Letter to my enemies, hey, I'm telling ya
Breaking you down to the level of molecular
Breaking you down to molecular level
Better be wise when you're choosing battles
Better be wise when choosing battles
Mostly babbles
You know one of those big time shady foe-foes
You know big time shady foes
Ain't worth fighting for
Drop these bars in my sleep, few more tricks up my sleeve
Drop bars in my sleep, tricks up my sleeve
It's way too late for you to leave now, get ready
Too late to leave now, get ready
Disturbing the peace
Look into my eyes
Now tell me the things
You blabbing about behind my back
You're blabbing about behind my back
The tenacity
The tenacity I hold
I hold it's hard to break down
It's hard to break down
It's too late for apologies
It's going down now
You're thirsty for blood
Actually craving for love
What you only want is dub
Greed makes you go numb
Purposefully blocking good thoughts
Hey, please doctor, doctor, he's 'bout to be that patient
Hey, doctor, he's 'bout to be that patient
'Cause I'm about to knock him out cold
Whole lotta moves i make on you like dance floor
Whole lotta moves I make on the dance floor
And during this beat down, you probably wish that you can fast forward
You probably wish you could fast forward
Don't you worry ' bout it, I'll save some room for your last words
Don't worry, I'll save room for your last words
After i do this, do that, and the third
Disturbing the peace
Look into my eyes
Now tell me the things
You blabbing about behind my back
You're blabbing about behind my back
The tenacity
The tenacity I hold
I hold it's hard to break down
It's hard to break down
It's too late for apologies
It's going down now
Some things may break me, but always get back up
New perspective gained from all the pain and stress
And when i do come back, I'm stronger than ever before
When I come back, I'm stronger than ever before
So kneel down
Disturbing the peace
Look into my eyes
Now tell me the things
You blabbing about behind my back
You're blabbing about behind my back
The tenacity
The tenacity I hold
I hold it's hard to break down
It's hard to break down
It's too late for apologies
It's going down now
Thank you so much everyone for listening!
Thank you, thank you.
Oh my gosh, that was so amazing. That was like a dream come true! Oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh, that was so amazing. That was
like a dream come true! Oh my gosh.
Thank you so much, everyone.
If you don't know who this is, introduce yourself.
I go by the name of Lotus Juice. Thank you for having me, Calli.
I go by the name of Lotus Juice.
Thank you for having me, Calli.
Thank you so much.
That was fun. That was fun.
Oh my gosh, it was seriously a dream of mine though just because...
Oh my gosh, it was seriously a dream of
mine though just because...
Really?
You know, I mean I've been a fan of your music like ever since high school, you know?
You know, I mean I've been a fan of your
music like ever since high school, you know?
That's just crazy.
I feel old, by the way.
Oh no, no, not at all. You you did not look at all. You are so awesome, oh my gosh.
Oh no, not at all. You did not look at all.
You are so awesome, oh my gosh.
A fangirl. Oh, my goodness. Thank you so much for being here, seriously.
A fangirl. Oh, my goodness. Thank you
so much for being here, seriously.
Like, Persona 3 is one of the things that like made me who I am, I think. Wow.
Like, Persona 3 is one of the things that
made me who I am, I think. Wow.
And um, like your your rap in that game was my first exposure ever to like, I guess, um, what I would call like J-rap, even though it's in English.
And like your rap in that game was my first
exposure to what I would call J-rap.
So, like that was the first time that I heard like a Japanese rapper and thought to yourself, "Oh my god, that's amazing. J-rap's so cool, you know, like..."
That was the first time I heard a Japanese
rapper and thought, "J-rap's so cool!"
Wow. Appreciate that. I mean, I did it like 18 years ago, and...
Wow. Appreciate that. I mean,
I did it like 18 years ago, and...
18 years ago?!
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I was a young rapper in Japan and trying to make it out there, having fun, and uh it's just crazy that, you know, people like you listen to it and now you're the the artist and uh so it's it's an honor to uh inspire people like you.
Yeah. I was a young rapper in Japan trying to
make it, and it's crazy people like you listen.
Thank you so much. Now, I mean, also J-rap is like kind of my roots now as well, which is why we have this show that's happening right now, you know? This is just incredible. Incredible.
Thank you so much. J-rap is like my roots
now too, which is why we have this show.
Yeah, it's awesome. You can join me in this like 3D world. It's like a transcendental experience.
Yeah, it's awesome. You can join me in this
3D world. It's a transcendental experience.
I love it, man. I love it.
Thank you so much for being here. And also thank you for singing with me on Sneaking Revenge as well from my album.
Thank you for being here, and for singing
with me on "Sneaking Revenge" from my album.
Oh, no doubt about that. I was that was a lot of fun. I mean, it was my first time not writing the lyrics, so it's like a cover song, but uh I met you uh the first time in a studio and uh we did it.
Oh, no doubt. It was a lot of fun, though
it was my first time not writing the lyrics.
Unfortunately, you had to leave early, but uh you know, we got to uh I I got to listen to your recording and you got to listen to mine and uh it was a lot of fun.
Unfortunately you had to leave early, but
we got to listen to each other's recordings.
Yeah.
Just getting to be in the studio together was seriously a a dream come true for me.
Just getting to be in the studio together was
seriously a dream come true for me.
So, thank you so much. And I always thought to myself that I wanted to have like a a male vocalist on the track as well, and you just fit perfectly 'cause...
I always wanted a male vocalist on the
track, and you just fit perfectly 'cause...
I don't know.
Great. You got like the coolest voice ever. Arigato!
Great! You got the coolest voice ever.
Arigato!
Oh man, that was awesome! Haha, wow. That was awesome.
Oh man, that was awesome! Haha, wow.
That was awesome.
I hope that we get a chance to collab again in the future someday on something.
I hope we get a chance to collab again in
the future someday on something.
For sure, no doubt, no doubt.
Cool. That would be awesome.
Well, sadly, we have to say goodbye to Lotus San for now, but...
Well, sadly, we have to say goodbye to
Lotus Juice for now, but...
...I hope you guys keep enjoying the final song, song of the night.
...I hope you guys keep enjoying the final
song, song of the night.
So, yes, last song, please enjoy you guys. Here here's the last song, enjoy.
So, yes, last song, please enjoy, you guys.
Here's the last song, enjoy!
Enjoy!
now listen, yo!
people put your guns up
まず 俺が run dat
First off, I run dat,
走りまわって 奴らを gun shot!!
running around and giving 'em a gunshot!!
brand new sound そう still survival
Brand new sound, yeah, still survival.
here come sound boy この世界に生きろ
Here come sound boy, live in this world.
知力体力と 運が舞うぜ! フロー
Wits, physical strength, and luck dance, flow!
ふくらんだ 頭中は ザックバラな なんだ!
Swollen, inside my head is all frank, what is this!
サバンナで バナナに ワンパン
In the savannah, one punch to a banana,
簡単 ノックアウト カンカンカン
easy knockout, clank clank clank.
one time for your mind 生き抜け
One time for your mind, survive through
around the world
つきまとうのさ いつもの痛みも
The usual pain clings on,
気高い 神のまわりも 今 借りもの
even the noble surroundings of God are borrowed now.
まかされた 種も 花咲けば 誰の?
Whose are the entrusted seeds once they bloom?
生きて 打ち込む 信念の矢を more more more
Living and firing arrows of conviction, more more more.
行き先に 安らぎはない
There is no peace ahead,
立ちなさい don't give up the fight
stand up, don't give up the fight.
今、そう この瞬間も die die die
Now, yeah, even at this moment, die die die.
big shooter 生き急いで blazing
Big shooter, living in a rush, blazing,
beat you up 切り開いて break
beat you up, cut through and break.
shot shooter 生き急いだ crazy
Shot shooter, living in a rush, crazy,
照準合う 至近距離で break
aligning sights, break at close range.
big shooter 生き急いで blazing
Big shooter, living in a rush, blazing,
beat you up 切り開いて break
beat you up, cut through and break.
shot shooter 生き急いだ crazy
Shot shooter, living in a rush, crazy,
照準合う 至近距離で break
aligning sights, break at close range.
link (link) up (up) super gun shooter
Link up, super gun shooter!
no boy can test we ホットネスさ light up!!
No boy can test we, hotness, light up!!
free (free) dom (dom) 陽暮れる前が ピーク
Freedom, right before sunset is the peak,
oh please 闘えば ピーク?
oh please, fight and it's peace?
swing (swing) chop (chop) 抜きな gun clap
Swing, chop, draw and gun clap,
真下で 揺らす 大地は ダンサブル
shaking right below, the earth is danceable.
rock (rock) your (your) body (body moving)
Rock your body moving,
朝まで grooving 速効 shooting
grooving till morning, fast-acting shooting.
un (un) un (un) un (un) un (un) un (un) un (un) un (un)
Un un un un un un un un...
We got a shoot, Samanosuke, yatsu ga kuru wa tobasu totte sketch down
We got a shoot, Samanosuke, they're coming, blow 'em away, sketch it down
I-K-U, S-A-K-U, Zen, crush!
暗くなる頃始まるパーティー 集める人種は箆々
As darkness falls, the party begins, gathering eccentric crowds,
明日なき夜にダークな遊び that’s my design さあ改造
in a dark night without a tomorrow, that's my design, now reform!
刺激が欲しい 命の限り
I want excitement, for as long as life lasts,
迷えるアタシと夜通し イイ？ あらあら あらあら
wandering with me all night long, ready? Oh my, oh my!
ホントは ずっと もう oh, oh
Truth is, all along, oh, oh,
楽しい フリして ay, ay
putting on a happy face, ay, ay,
消えた アタシ を oh, oh
the me that disappeared, oh, oh,
キミ が 見つけて ねほら
you'll find me, hey, look!
フラフラ する でしょう クラクラ 来る でしょう
Must be swaying, must be dizzy,
ホロホロ とろけ そう そうでしょう flash bang
melting away softly, right? Flash bang!
フラフラ する でしょう クラクラ 来る でしょう
Must be swaying, must be dizzy,
そろそろ 壊れ そう そうでしょう flash bang
about to break down soon, right? Flash bang!
flash bang
まどろむ underground 浮快い た 開放 感
Drowsy underground, a fleeting sense of release,
剥がれた ペルソナ 放り投げ break it down
shedding the persona and throwing it away, break it down!
だんだん 壊れ て く 感覚 染まる の は 息 する 様 に カンタン
The sensation of gradually falling apart, getting dyed is as easy as breathing.
変わっ ていく アタシ 時 は 待った なし 涙 を 潤し あらあら あらあら
The changing me, time waits for no one, wiping away tears, oh my, oh my!
いやぁ まぁ なんか 転生した ？ uh
Oh well, somehow I reincarnated? Huh?
みたいな 異世界 感 纏って 違う 人 みたい だ
Wrapped in an isekai vibe, I look like a completely different person.
そりゃ あ 今日 も お美しい 出会っ て 思った んだ よ you choose me
No wonder I thought you were so gorgeous today when we met, you choose me.
けれど あの 頃 の 君 は もう マ ボロシ の 様 に フッ となくなりそう
But you from back then is about to vanish like a phantom.
それが フラッシュ し て バック する ん だ 目 が 回る ん だ グルグル グルグル
Then it flashes and bounces back, making my head spin round and round.
ホント は きっと もう oh, oh
Truth is, surely, oh, oh,
戻れ ない ほど ね ay, ay
to the point of no return, ay, ay,
ちらつく 心 oh, oh
flickering heart, oh, oh,
キミ が 探し て よほら
you go and search for it, hey, look!
フラフラ する でしょう クラクラ 来る でしょう
Must be swaying, must be dizzy,
ホロホロ とろけ そう そうでしょう flash bang
melting away softly, right? Flash bang!
ギラギラ 今宵 の show さあさあ 踊り ましょ う
Dazzling tonight's show, come on, let's dance!
真白く 目眩む ほど ほら 焼き付け て よ flash bang
Blindingly pure white, burn it into your eyes, flash bang!
flash bang
Big shooter
生き急いで blazing
Living in a rush, blazing
beat you up 切り開いて break
Beat you up, carving a path, break!
Shot shooter
生き急いで crazy
Living in a rush, crazy
照準合わす 至近距離で break
Aligning sights, breaking at close range!
Big shooter
生き急いで blazing
Living in a rush, blazing
beat you up 切り開いて break
Beat you up, carving a path, break!
Shot shooter
生き急いで crazy
Living in a rush, crazy
照準合わす 至近距離で break
Aligning sights, breaking at close range!
Yo, Dead Beats! Did you enjoy the show?
I've got a couple more announcements for you before we head off to the MV premiere and then the members-only encore performance at 9:15 JST, so don't head out yet, okay?
I've got a couple more announcements before the MV premiere and encore at 9:15 JST, so don't leave yet!
はい、お知らせあります！
Yes, we have announcements!
You know what time it is? Goods time!
These are technically to celebrate my fourth anniversary, but they're themed around today's show. So that's right, goods arimasu!
These celebrate my 4th anniversary, themed around today's show. So yes, goods are here!
First off, we've got a poster from the Underground.
It's a huge poster of me, Mori Calliope, in underworldian street fashion promoting my live show, a nice memory of Neo Tokyo. とっても素敵なポスターです！
It's a huge poster of me in underworldian street fashion. It's a wonderful poster!
Want to write lyrics, scribble doodles,
write letters to fictional characters about everyone who bullied you in school,
or write letters to fictional characters about everyone who bullied you in school?
Grab a Mori themed notebook! It's a super cute design with lots of mini Moris running around it, so make it yours today! とっても素敵なノートです！
Grab a Mori notebook! It's a super cute design with mini Moris. It's a wonderful notebook!
Are you ready to shed your mortal coil and become an actual skeleton?
Well, if you did that, Mori would get in trouble. So how about a Dead Beat themed hoodie as a regular old skeleton, but cooler.
How about a Dead Beat themed hoodie? You can also use it as a Halloween costume!
It's super comfy, so make sure you grab it! とっても素敵なパーカーです！
It's super comfy, so grab yours! It's a wonderful hoodie!
Finally we have... Oh god. Oh god, no, wait, not that thing. Wait, wait, Manager-chan, Manager-chan!
Finally we have... Oh god. Oh no, wait, not that thing. Manager-chan!
Wasn't there something else we were selling? Like a water bottle or something? Why is weird freaking cat here?
Wasn't there something else we were selling, like a water bottle? Why is this weird cat here?
Uh... Okay, I'm being told to roll with it.
Okay, I'm being told to roll with it.
Weird cat is here as a cute plushie for your collection. Just look, if you buy this thing, be careful, okay?
Weird cat is here as a cute plushie for your collection. Be careful if you buy this!
I don't claim any responsibility for whatever happens to you after. とっても怖いぬいぐるみです！
I claim no responsibility for what happens after. It's a terrifying plushie!
If you buy all pieces of merch, you'll get this, a sticker sheet full of mini Moris.
If you buy all merch pieces, you get this sticker sheet full of mini Moris.
Stick them onto your car, your computer, your little brother's switch and see how angry he gets!
Stick them on your car, computer, or your little brother's Switch!
I don't know, they're your stickers now, so do whatever you want with them I guess. ステッカーもらいまーす！
Do whatever you want with your stickers! ステッカーもらいまーす！
Now the merch is out of the way, let's talk about my brand new song releasing! That's right folks, a brand new J-rap single titled "FLASH BANG" is coming out right after this stream with PES-san!
Now, let's talk about my new song! A brand new J-rap single "FLASH BANG" with PES-san!
In Japan, a member of Rip Sslime who helped popularize the entire genre,
Rip SslimeのPESさんと一緒にコラボしました！
teamed up with PES of Rip Sslime!
やった！パチパチパチパチパチ！
Yay! Clap clap clap clap clap!
もうすぐMVリリースしますよ。
The MV will be released soon.
We got a special message from him too. So, let's run the clip.
デッドビーツの皆さんこんにちは、
Hello, Deadbeats!
ペスと申します。
I'm PES.
カリオペさんの「Super Shooter」、え、いかがでしたでございましたでしょうか？
What did you think of Calliope's "Super Shooter"?
え、このたび私、え、ペスがですね、カリオペさんとコラボをさせていただくことになりました。
This time I, PES, had the chance to collaborate with Calliope!
はい、ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much!
えー私がねプロデュースさせていただいたカリオペさんの新曲、「FLASH BANG」がですねリリースされることになりました。
I was able to produce Calliope's new song, "FLASH BANG" which is being released now!
よいしょ、ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
え、この曲はですね、あの、まあライブ、皆さん楽しみに、え、カリオペさんのライブ見ていただいてると思うんですけども、
So about this song, I think everyone is really enjoying watching Calliope's Live
そのライブね、こう終わった後だったらいろんな普段の生活の中でもこうパットね、こう連れ戻されるような、パット思い出してしまうような、そんな瞬間が、
and that Live, once it is over, during your normal everyday life, there are instances where you are just suddenly brought back and just suddenly remember.
え、彼女のこの魅力の中にあるんじゃないかなっていうことで、ですね、
Her ability to make people feel that is one of her strong points I feel.
こうパット、一瞬ふっと、その瞬間に戻ってしまえるような、
Suddenly, in one moment, in that instance you remember the song.
そんな楽しい、え、曲に、なっておるか、と、思われますので、
That fun type of song is what I think we were able to make,
え、ぜひ皆さん、え、聞いてみてください。
so everyone be sure to listen to it!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you!
Thank you so much PES-san! Another one of my big dreams has come true.
I hope you guys loop this song lots and enjoy the super cute animated music video.
It really encapsulates my love for Japanese rap and I hope those feelings come through to all of you when you listen.
Thanks again for tuning in everyone! Keep enjoying J-Rap,
keep enjoying Mori, keep enjoying things that make you happy! Catch you on the flip side, and hopefully at the premiere and member's encore! Peace!